so my
wife has been visiting her sister in l.a
for a couple weeks now
and uh i miss her so much
and i've been finding myself feeling so
deeply appreciative of her
i'm normally really appreciative of her
but there's a way where she's
been so present in my aloneness
to tell you man there are so many
different kinds of alone
and not all of them are pleasant for
sure
in fact i would say there's a way in
which being alone
one can really something about the
spaciousness
of being alone
that somehow probably makes
room for the character
i would say probably of all experience
really
you have these
multiple horizons
these multiple apprehensions
and i think one of the things i've been
so appreciative with
my wife
is that part of what's made this
two weeks for me so awesome
is the way in which she's been here
by that there's i guess in
i guess in some way i know musicians
talk about this that really
music is all about conditioning the
silence
that the music is actually shaping
the silent note
and i think i'm appreciating the music
of her end of our relationship
and who she is
to me and who she is for us
and in some way in a very primary way
i can feel it as animating
the way the solitude is present for me
for example you know if say
we were in a fight or the relationship
was not working
or something like that and
like she went away and
we were mad at each other or something
like that
i imagine it'd be a very different alone
so i think in a lot of ways i'm
um
present through her absence of how
grateful i am
to be able to be someone
and which i so thoroughly enjoy spending
time with on myself is as much
a function of her as it
is of anything about me
so i guess in some way
like every moment is filled with these
horizons of anticipation of all the
different
things that the sense of what could
happen
the talos of the moment
what's likely to happen all of the
things that i probably don't
actually need to even represent in my
mind but live
in a kind of
horizon
that reveals itself as the sense of the
moment
as the mood that attunes
the very being of the moment
is
uh